criny.com 2010-12-11

# Market Force | Privacy Policy

### Shopper Privacy Statement  
Updated January 1, 2008

### Introduction

While information is the cornerstone of our ability to provide superior service to our clients, our most important asset is our Shoppers’ trust. Respecting and protecting your privacy has been vital to our business for more than 35 years. At Market Force Information™, Inc., we understand your concerns about privacy and have created this Privacy Policy and Statement in order to demonstrate our strong commitment to the privacy of our Mystery Shoppers and the personal information that they share with us. This Statement describes the type(s) of information we collect, how it is handled, and with whom it is shared. As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, this Policy will most likely change. Therefore, we encourage you to refer to this Policy on an ongoing basis.

### What do we do with your Shopper information?

We treat all the information collected at this site as highly confidential. We will never give or sell confidential or personal information (including your email address) about our Shoppers to any third party except as required by law, pursuant to our Shopping Service Agreements, or when we verify your identity before we accept you as a Shopper. Keeping secure the personal information you have shared with us is a top priority for everyone at Market Force Information.

### What kind of information do we have, and where did we get it?

Most of the information that we have comes directly from you. When submitting your Application or Contractor Information Sheet, you give us information such as your name, address, and Social Security number. We also keep historical information about your mystery shopping assignments such as the types of assignments you have completed and how much you have been paid for Shopping for us. Occasionally we may ask for your participation in surveys and obtain additional personal information from you regarding your buying habits, shopping preferences, and other personal information related to the surveys. Participation in these surveys will always be optional, as this information may be shared with others. Only the survey results and broad demographic information will be shared, not any of your personally identifiable information.

### How do we protect your personal information?

Internally, only a limited number of trusted Market Force Information employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Each of these employees has signed a binding Confidentiality Agreement and Non-Disclosure Agreement as a condition of their employment with Market Force Information. To log in to our proprietary system that contains information about you, our employees must enter a registered password and are granted permission to enter the system only after receiving training on how to handle personal information. The servers where we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure, locked environment with restricted access safe behind our corporate firewalls. We have established physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your information. Should your relationship with Market Force Information end, your information will remain protected in accordance with our practices as outlined in this Privacy Statement.

### Changes in Personal Information

Market Force Information’s website will allow Market Force Information Mystery Shoppers options for changing, modifying, or deleting personally identifiable information previously submitted to Market Force Information. Options will include an email address which can be used to request one of our employees to make the change in the database as well as a method for the Shopper to personally change the information in our database. It will be the Shopper’s option as to which method to choose.

### Children

Market Force Information’s website is not intended for children and all Market Force Information Mystery Shoppers must be more than 20 years old. Market Force Information realizes that children are active on the Internet, but we do not knowingly collect any information from children. There are tools available from online services and software manufacturers that can prevent children from disclosing name, address, and other personal information online without parental permission.

### Email Communications

Our software does not encrypt email messages. Email messages traveling through the Internet are subject to viewing, alteration, and copying by potentially anyone on the Internet. Please keep in mind that transmitting information via email over the Internet is never completely secure and thus any information submitted may be intercepted, collected, used, or disclosed by others. If you are concerned about the security of your communication(s), we encourage you to send your correspondence through the United States Postal Service or use the telephone to speak directly to us. We are not responsible for the security or confidentiality of communications you send to us through the Internet using email messages.

### Use of Cookies

A “cookie” is a small amount of text that a website can send to the browser on your hard drive to assist in distinguishing your browser from a previous visitor by saving and remembering any preferences that may have been set while visiting a particular site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and most major websites use them. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser to erase cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

We want to assure visitors of the Market Force Information website that accepting a cookie does not give us access to information stored on their computers, or provide us with any user information, nor does a cookie take up any significant hard drive space. At Market Force Information we do not currently use cookies on a regular basis, but we may decide to begin using this technology in the future on a very limited basis. We will revise this Statement accordingly if we elect to begin using this technology on a regular and routine basis, so you may wish to check this policy periodically for updates.

### Collection of Information

When you browse the Market Force Information website at [www.marketforce.com](http://www.marketforce.com/) your email address is not automatically collected. Our web server automatically gathers and logs the following information about your visit: your Internet domain name and IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the pages you visit, and the date and time of your visit. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use this information primarily to learn about the number of people who visit our site and the technology used in order to assist in developing changes to our website, to improve the content of our website, and for business planning purposes.

### What can you do to help maintain the security of information when accessing Market Force Information over the Internet?

  * Utilize the latest, generally proven (not a test or “beta” release) version of Netscape, Microsoft Internet Explorer, or another Internet browser.
  * Keep your Shopper ID and Password confidential.
  * Make sure others are not watching you enter your Shopper ID or password on your keyboard.
  * Never use the option that will allow your ID or password to be saved on your computer.
  * Do not leave your computer unattended while logged on to our website. After you have finished accessing the information you need, exit the Shopper Website. This helps ensure that no one can access your information if you leave your computer on.

### Notification of Changes

This privacy statement was last updated on January 1, 2008. If we significantly change or modify our privacy policies, we will post notification to all users on our Shopper Message Board for a period of at least one (1) week.

### Privacy Policy Contact

Anyone with questions concerning the use of personal information by Market Force Information or security on our website may contact: The Legal Department, Market Force Information, (303) 402.6920, 248 Centennial Parkway, Suite 150, Louisville, CO 80027.
